{"Questions": { "Question #1 Topic 1":{ "question":"Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?", "answers":[ "A. Ensuring that disk drives are wiped after use.", "B. Ensuring that firmware is updated on hardware devices.", "CORRECT:C. Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest.", "D. Ensuring that network cables are category six or higher."],"explanation": "AWS for a self-hosted database that requires a nightly shutdown for maintenance and cost-saving purposes","discussions": "22"}, "Question #2 Topic 1":{ "question":"The use of what AWS feature or service allows companies to track and categorize spending on a detailed level?", "answers":[ "A. Cost allocation tags", "B. Consolidated billing", "CORRECT:C. AWS Budgets", "D. AWS Marketplace"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/startups/how-to-set-aws-budget-when-paying-with-aws-credits/","discussions": "38"}, "Question #3 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service stores objects, provides real-time access to those objects, and offers versioning and lifecycle capabilities?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Glacier", "B. AWS Storage Gateway", "CORRECT:C. Amazon S3", "D. Amazon EBS"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #4 Topic 1":{ "question":"What AWS team assists customers with accelerating cloud adoption through paid engagements in any of several specialty practice areas?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Enterprise Support", "B. AWS Solutions Architects", "CORRECT:C. AWS Professional Services", "D. AWS Account Managers"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/professional-services/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #5 Topic 1":{ "question":"A customer would like to design and build a new workload on AWS Cloud but does not have the AWS-related software technical expertise in-house. Which of the following AWS programs can a customer take advantage of to achieve that outcome?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Partner Network Technology Partners", "B. AWS Marketplace", "CORRECT:C. AWS Partner Network Consulting Partners", "D. AWS Service Catalog"],"explanation": "","discussions": "14"}, "Question #6 Topic 1":{ "question":"Distributing workloads across multiple Availability Zones supports which cloud architecture design principle?", "answers":[ "A. Implement automation.", "B. Design for agility.", "CORRECT:C. Design for failure.", "D. Implement elasticity."],"explanation": "","discussions": "22"}, "Question #7 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon EC2", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)", "C. Amazon Aurora", "D. Amazon Redshift", "E. Amazon S3"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/sql/","discussions": "12"}, "Question #8 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following inspects AWS environments to find opportunities that can save money for users and also improve system performance?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Cost Explorer", "CORRECT:B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. Consolidated billing", "D. Detailed billing"],"explanation": "","discussions": "14"}, "Question #9 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models allow customers to use existing server-bound software licenses?", "answers":[ "A. Spot Instances", "B. Reserved Instances", "CORRECT:C. Dedicated Hosts", "D. On-Demand Instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #10 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. High availability", "B. Shared security model", "CORRECT:C. Elasticity", "CORRECT:D. Pay-as-you-go pricing", "E. Reliability"],"explanation": "","discussions": "5"}, "Question #11 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service enables risk auditing by continuously monitoring and logging account activity, including user actions in the AWS Management Console and AWS SDKs?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon CloudWatch", "CORRECT:B. AWS CloudTrail", "C. AWS Config", "D. AWS Health"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #12 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. A global file system", "CORRECT:B. An object store", "C. A local file store", "D. A network file system", "E. A durable storage system"],"explanation": "","discussions": "39"}, "Question #13 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Route 53", "CORRECT:B. Virtual Private Gateway", "C. Classic Load Balancer", "D. Auto Scaling", "E. Amazon CloudWatch default metrics"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.stratoscale.com/blog/cloud/building-hybrid-cloud-environment-using-amazon-cloud/","discussions": "21"}, "Question #14 Topic 1":{ "question":"What costs are included when comparing AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) with on-premises TCO?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Project management", "B. Antivirus software licensing", "C. Data center security", "D. Software development"],"explanation": "","discussions": "35"}, "Question #15 Topic 1":{ "question":"A company is considering using AWS for a self-hosted database that requires a nightly shutdown for maintenance and cost-saving purposes. Which service should the company use?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Redshift", "B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) with Amazon EC2 instance store", "CORRECT:D. Amazon EC2 with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"],"explanation": "","discussions": "26"}, "Question #16 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is a correct relationship between regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations?", "answers":[ "A. Data centers contain regions.", "CORRECT:B. Regions contain Availability Zones.", "C. Availability Zones contain edge locations.", "D. Edge locations contain regions."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/#Region_Maps_and_Edge_Networks","discussions": "7"}, "Question #17 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs? (Choose three.)", "answers":[ "A. Detailed billing report", "CORRECT:B. Cost allocation tags", "CORRECT:C. AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "CORRECT:D. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "E. Cost Estimator"],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #18 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are advantages of AWS consolidated billing? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts", "B. Service limits increasing by default in all accounts", "C. A fixed discount on the monthly bill", "CORRECT:D. Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined", "E. The automatic extension of the master account's AWS support plan to all accounts"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","discussions": "8"}, "Question #19 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following Reserved Instance (RI) pricing models provides the highest average savings compared to On-Demand pricing?", "answers":[ "A. One-year, No Upfront, Standard RI pricing", "B. One-year, All Upfront, Convertible RI pricing", "CORRECT:C. Three-year, All Upfront, Standard RI pricing", "D. Three-year, No Upfront, Convertible RI pricing"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","discussions": "6"}, "Question #20 Topic 1":{ "question":"Compared with costs in traditional and virtualized data centers, AWS has:", "answers":[ "A. greater variable costs and greater upfront costs.", "B. fixed usage costs and lower upfront costs.", "C. lower variable costs and greater upfront costs.", "CORRECT:D. lower variable costs and lower upfront costs."],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/introduction-to-aws-cloud-economics-final.pdf (10)","discussions": "3"}, "Question #21 Topic 1":{ "question":"A characteristic of edge locations is that they:", "answers":[ "A. host Amazon EC2 instances closer to users.", "B. help lower latency and improve performance for users.", "CORRECT:C. cache frequently changing data without reaching the origin server.", "D. refresh data changes daily."],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.edureka.co/community/600/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws","discussions": "46"}, "Question #22 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following can limit Amazon Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket access to specific users?", "answers":[ "A. A public and private key-pair", "B. Amazon Inspector", "CORRECT:C. AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies", "D. Security Groups"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/how-to-restrict-amazon-s3-bucket-access-to-a-specific-iam-role/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #23 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following security-related actions are available at no cost?", "answers":[ "A. Calling AWS Support", "B. Contacting AWS Professional Services to request a workshop", "CORRECT:C. Accessing forums, blogs, and whitepapers", "D. Attending AWS classes at a local university"],"explanation": "","discussions": "11"}, "Question #24 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the Reserved Instance (RI) pricing models can change the attributes of the RI as long as the exchange results in the creation of RIs of equal or greater value?", "answers":[ "A. Dedicated RIs", "B. Scheduled RIs", "CORRECT:C. Convertible RIs", "D. Standard RIs"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #25 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS feature will reduce the customer's total cost of ownership (TCO)?", "answers":[ "A. Shared responsibility security model", "B. Single tenancy", "CORRECT:C. Elastic computing", "D. Encryption"],"explanation": "","discussions": "28"}, "Question #26 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following services will automatically scale with an expected increase in web traffic?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CodePipeline", "CORRECT:B. Elastic Load Balancing", "C. Amazon EBS", "D. AWS Direct Connect"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","discussions": "21"}, "Question #27 Topic 1":{ "question":"Where are AWS compliance documents, such as an SOC 1 report, located?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Inspector", "B. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:C. AWS Artifact", "D. AWS Certificate Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/soc-faqs/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #28 Topic 1":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following activities are the customer's responsibility? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Patching operating system components for Amazon Relational Database Server (Amazon RDS)", "CORRECT:B. Encrypting data on the client-side", "C. Training the data center staff", "CORRECT:D. Configuring Network Access Control Lists (ACL)", "E. Maintaining environmental controls within a data center"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #29 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which is a recommended pattern for designing a highly available architecture on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Ensure that components have low-latency network connectivity.", "B. Run enough Amazon EC2 instances to operate at peak load.", "CORRECT:C. Ensure that the application is designed to accommodate failure of any single component.", "D. Use a monolithic application that handles all operations."],"explanation": "","discussions": "15"}, "Question #30 Topic 1":{ "question":"According to best practices, how should an application be designed to run in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Use tighly coupled components.", "CORRECT:B. Use loosely coupled components.", "C. Use infrequently coupled components.", "D. Use frequently coupled components."],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","discussions": "5"}, "Question #31 Topic 1":{ "question":"AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Implementing Amazon Rekognition", "B. Using AWS Shield-protected resources", "C. Blocking access with Security Groups", "CORRECT:D. Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)", "CORRECT:E. Enforcing password strength and expiration"],"explanation": "","discussions": "16"}, "Question #32 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Glacier", "CORRECT:B. Amazon RDS", "C. AWS Snowball", "D. Amazon Redshift", "E. Amazon EFS"],"explanation": "","discussions": "42"}, "Question #33 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is one of the advantages of the Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. It simplifies relational database administration tasks.", "B. It provides 99.99999999999% reliability and durability.", "C. It automatically scales databases for loads.", "D. It enabled users to dynamically adjust CPU and RAM resources."],"explanation": "","discussions": "22"}, "Question #34 Topic 1":{ "question":"A customer needs to run a MySQL database that easily scales. Which AWS service should they use?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Aurora", "B. Amazon Redshift", "C. Amazon DynamoDB", "D. Amazon ElastiCache"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/serverless/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #35 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following components of the AWS Global Infrastructure consists of one or more discrete data centers interconnected through low latency links?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Availability Zone", "B. Edge location", "C. Region", "D. Private networking"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/global-infrastructure.html","discussions": "16"}, "Question #36 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is a shared control between the customer and AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Providing a key for Amazon S3 client-side encryption", "B. Configuration of an Amazon EC2 instance", "C. Environmental controls of physical AWS data centers", "CORRECT:D. Awareness and training"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "14"}, "Question #37 Topic 1":{ "question":"How many Availability Zones should compute resources be provisioned across to achieve high availability?", "answers":[ "A. A minimum of one", "CORRECT:B. A minimum of two", "C. A minimum of three", "D. A minimum of four or more"],"explanation": "","discussions": "16"}, "Question #38 Topic 1":{ "question":"One of the advantages to moving infrastructure from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud is:", "answers":[ "A. it allows the business to eliminate IT bills.", "B. it allows the business to put a server in each customer's data center.", "CORRECT:C. it allows the business to focus on business activities.", "D. it allows the business to leave servers unpatched."],"explanation": "","discussions": "11"}, "Question #39 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is the lowest-cost, durable storage option for retaining database backups for immediate retrieval?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon S3", "B. Amazon Glacier", "C. Amazon EBS", "D. Amazon EC2 Instance Store"],"explanation": "","discussions": "18"}, "Question #40 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS IAM feature allows developers to access AWS services through the AWS CLI?", "answers":[ "A. API keys", "B. Access keys", "C. User names/Passwords", "CORRECT:D. SSH keys"],"explanation": "","discussions": "34"}, "Question #41 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is a fast and reliable NoSQL database service?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Redshift", "B. Amazon RDS", "CORRECT:C. Amazon DynamoDB", "D. Amazon S3"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #42 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is an example of agility in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Access to multiple instance types", "B. Access to managed services", "C. Using Consolidated Billing to produce one bill", "CORRECT:D. Decreased acquisition time for new compute resources"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/enterprise-strategy/risk-is-lack-of-agility/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #43 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service should a customer use to consolidate and centrally manage multiple AWS accounts?", "answers":[ "A. AWS IAM", "CORRECT:B. AWS Organizations", "C. AWS Schema Conversion Tool", "D. AWS Config"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #44 Topic 1":{ "question":"What approach to transcoding a large number of individual video files adheres to AWS architecture principles?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Using many instances in parallel", "B. Using a single large instance during off-peak hours", "C. Using dedicated hardware", "D. Using a large GPU instance type"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/solutions/case-studies/encoding/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #45 Topic 1":{ "question":"For which auditing process does AWS have sole responsibility?", "answers":[ "A. AWS IAM policies", "CORRECT:B. Physical security", "C. Amazon S3 bucket policies", "D. AWS CloudTrail Logs"],"explanation": "","discussions": "7"}, "Question #46 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which feature of the AWS Cloud will support an international company's requirement for low latency to all of its customers?", "answers":[ "A. Fault tolerance", "CORRECT:B. Global reach", "C. Pay-as-you-go pricing", "D. High availability"],"explanation": "","discussions": "18"}, "Question #47 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is the customer's responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?", "answers":[ "A. Patching underlying infrastructure", "B. Physical security", "CORRECT:C. Patching Amazon EC2 instances", "D. Patching network infrastructure"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #48 Topic 1":{ "question":"A customer is using multiple AWS accounts with separate billing. How can the customer take advantage of volume discounts with minimal impact to the AWS resources?", "answers":[ "A. Create one global AWS acount and move all AWS resources to tha account.", "B. Sign up for three years of Reserved Instance pricing up front.", "CORRECT:C. Use the consolidated billing feature from AWS Organizations.", "D. Sign up for the AWS Enterprise support plan to get volume discounts."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/answers/account-management/aws-multi-account-billing-strategy/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #49 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)", "B. Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics", "C. Provided at no charge", "CORRECT:D. Real-time monitoring", "CORRECT:E. Adjustable retention"],"explanation": "","discussions": "21"}, "Question #50 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is an AWS managed Domain Name System (DNS) web service?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Route 53", "B. Amazon Neptune", "C. Amazon SageMaker", "D. Amazon Lightsail"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/get-a-domain/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #51 Topic 1":{ "question":"A customer is deploying a new application and needs to choose an AWS Region. Which of the following factors could influence the customer's decision? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Reduced latency to users", "B. The application's presentation in the local language", "CORRECT:C. Data sovereignty compliance", "D. Cooling costs in hotter climates", "E. Proximity to the customer's office for on-site visits"],"explanation": "","discussions": "12"}, "Question #52 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which storage service can be used as a low-cost option for hosting static websites?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Glacier", "B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/projects/host-static-website/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #53 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing model can provide discounts of up to 90%?", "answers":[ "A. Reserved Instances", "B. On-Demand", "C. Dedicated Hosts", "CORRECT:D. Spot Instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/spot/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #54 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is the AWS customer responsible for according to the AWS shared responsibility model?", "answers":[ "A. Physical access controls", "CORRECT:B. Data encryption", "C. Secure disposal of storage devices", "D. Environmental risk management"],"explanation": "","discussions": "4"}, "Question #55 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following AWS Cloud services can be used to run a customer-managed relational database?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon EC2", "B. Amazon Route 53", "C. Amazon ElastiCache", "D. Amazon DynamoDB"],"explanation": "","discussions": "17"}, "Question #56 Topic 1":{ "question":"A company is looking for a scalable data warehouse solution. Which of the following AWS solutions would meet the company's needs?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)", "B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon Kinesis", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Redshift"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #57 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which statement best describes Elastic Load Balancing?", "answers":[ "A. It translates a domain name into an IP address using DNS.", "CORRECT:B. It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances.", "C. It collects metrics on connected Amazon EC2 instances.", "D. It automatically adjusts the number of Amazon EC2 instances to support incoming traffic."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #58 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Command line interface", "B. On-premises", "CORRECT:C. Software Development Kits", "D. Software-as-a-service", "E. Hybrid"],"explanation": "","discussions": "4"}, "Question #59 Topic 1":{ "question":"The AWS Cloud's multiple Regions are an example of:", "answers":[ "A. agility.", "CORRECT:B. global infrastructure.", "C. elasticity.", "D. pay-as-you-go pricing."],"explanation": "","discussions": "13"}, "Question #60 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Storage Gateway", "CORRECT:B. Amazon S3", "C. Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)", "D. Amazon Glacier", "CORRECT:E. Amazom CloudFront"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/deliver-content-faster/ https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","discussions": "6"}, "Question #61 Topic 1":{ "question":"Web servers running on Amazon EC2 access a legacy application running in a corporate data center. What term would describe this model?", "answers":[ "A. Cloud-native", "B. Partner network", "CORRECT:C. Hybrid architecture", "D. Infrastructure as a service"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/enterprise/hybrid/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #62 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is the benefit of using AWS managed services, such as Amazon ElastiCache and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?", "answers":[ "A. They require the customer to monitor and replace failing instances.", "CORRECT:B. They have better performance than customer-managed services.", "C. They simplify patching and updating underlying OSs.", "D. They do not require the customer to optimize instance type or size selections."],"explanation": "","discussions": "48"}, "Question #63 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service provides a virtually unlimited amount of online highly durable object storage?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Redshift", "B. Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)", "C. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)", "CORRECT:D. Amazon S3"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-object-storage/","discussions": "11"}, "Question #64 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following Identity and Access Management (IAM) entities is associated with an access key ID and secret access key when using AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)?", "answers":[ "A. IAM group", "B. IAM user", "C. IAM role", "CORRECT:D. IAM policy"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_access-keys.html","discussions": "37"}, "Question #65 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Multi-factor authentication physical tokens", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor security checks", "CORRECT:C. Data encryption", "CORRECT:D. Automated penetration testing", "E. Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/security/","discussions": "32"}, "Question #66 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS managed service is used to host databases?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Batch", "B. AWS Artifact", "C. AWS Data Pipeline", "CORRECT:D. Amazon RDS"],"explanation": "Explanation - Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) makes it easy to set up, operate, and scale a relational database in the cloud. It provides cost-efficient and resizable capacity while automating time-consuming administration tasks such as hardware provisioning, database setup, patching and backups. It frees you to focus on your applications so you can give them the fast performance, high availability, security and compatibility they need. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/rds/?c=db&sec=srv","discussions": "1"}, "Question #67 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides a simple and scalable shared file storage solution for use with Linux-based AWS and on-premises servers?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon S3", "B. Amazon Glacier", "C. Amazon EBS", "CORRECT:D. Amazon EFS"],"explanation": "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) provides a simple, scalable, fully managed elastic NFS file system for use with AWS Cloud services and on-premises resources. It is built to scale on demand to petabytes without disrupting applications, growing and shrinking automatically as you add and remove files, eliminating the need to provision and manage capacity to accommodate growth. Amazon EFS is designed to provide the throughput, IOPS, and low latency needed for Linux workloads. Throughput and IOPS scale as a file system grows and can burst to higher throughput levels for short periods of time to support the unpredictable performance needs of file workloads. For the most demanding workloads, Amazon EFS can support performance over 10 GB/sec and up to 500,000 IOPS.","discussions": "10"}, "Question #68 Topic 1":{ "question":"When architecting cloud applications, which of the following are a key design principle?", "answers":[ "A. Use the largest instance possible", "CORRECT:B. Provision capacity for peak load", "C. Use the Scrum development process", "D. Implement elasticity"],"explanation": "Cloud services main proposition is to provide elasticity through horizontal scaling. It's already there. As for using largest instance possible, it is not a design principle that helps cloud applications in anyway. Scrum development process is not related to architecting. Therefore, a key principle is to provision your application for on-demand capacity. Peak loads is something that cloud applications experience everyday. Peak load management should be a necessary part of cloud application design principle. Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","discussions": "25"}, "Question #69 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service should be used for long-term, low-cost storage of data backups?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon RDS", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Glacier", "C. AWS Snowball", "D. AWS EBS"],"explanation": "Explanation - Amazon S3 Glacier is a secure, durable, and low-cost storage class of S3 for data archiving and long-term backup. Customers can store large or small amounts of data for as little as $0.004 per gigabyte per month. The S3 Glacier storage class is ideal for archives where data is regularly retrieved and some of the data may be needed in minutes. Amazon RDS is a relational database service that hosts databases. It helps you create and manage databases. Amazon Snowball is a petabyte-scale data transfer service that provides cost efficient data transfer to AWS from tamper proof physical devices. Similarly, Elastic block storage offers persistent block storage volumes for EC2 instances. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/backup-restore/services/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #70 Topic 1":{ "question":"Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is a shared control between a customer and AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Physical controls", "CORRECT:B. Patch management", "C. Zone security", "D. Data center auditing"],"explanation": "","discussions": "18"}, "Question #71 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service allows companies to connect an Amazon VPC to an on-premises data center?", "answers":[ "A. AWS VPN", "B. Amazon Redshift", "C. API Gateway", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Direct Connect"],"explanation": "AWS Direct Connect enables you to securely connect your AWS environment to your on-premises data center or office location over a standard 1 gigabit or 10 gigabit Ethernet fiber-optic connection. AWS Direct Connect offers dedicated high speed, low latency connection, which bypasses internet service providers in your network path. An AWS Direct Connect location provides access to Amazon Web Services in the region it is associated with, as well as access to other US regions. AWS Direct Connect allows you to logically partition the fiber-optic connections into multiple logical connections called Virtual Local Area Networks (VLAN). You can take advantage of these logical connections to improve security, differentiate traffic, and achieve compliance requirements. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/projects/connect-data-center-to-aws/","discussions": "13"}, "Question #72 Topic 1":{ "question":"A company wants to reduce the physical compute footprint that developers use to run code. Which service would meet that need by enabling serverless architectures?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)", "CORRECT:B. AWS Lambda", "C. Amazon DynamoDB", "D. AWS CodeCommit"],"explanation": "AWS Lambda is an integral part of coding on AWS. It reduces physical compute footprint by utilizing aws cloud services to run code.","discussions": "5"}, "Question #73 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides alerts when an AWS event may impact a company's AWS resources?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "B. AWS Service Health Dashboard", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "D. AWS Infrastructure Event Management"],"explanation": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard provides alerts and remediation guidance when AWS is experiencing events that may impact you. While the Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, Personal Health Dashboard gives you a personalized view into the performance and availability of the AWS services underlying your AWS resources. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/personal-health-dashboard/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #74 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Fault Tolerance", "B. Instance Usage", "C. Infrastructure", "CORRECT:D. Performance", "E. Storage Capacity"],"explanation": "Like your customized cloud expert, AWS Trusted Advisor analyzes your AWS environment and provides best practice recommendations in five categories: cost optimization, performance, security, fault tolerance and service limits. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #75 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which task is AWS responsible for in the shared responsibility model for security and compliance?", "answers":[ "A. Granting access to individuals and services", "CORRECT:B. Encrypting data in transit", "C. Updating Amazon EC2 host firmware", "D. Updating operating systems"],"explanation": "AWS Compliance enables customers to establish and operate in an AWS security control environment ✑ The shared responsibility model is part of AWS Compliance program ✑ The Security of the cloud is managed by Amazon AWS provider ✑ The Security in the cloud is responsibility of the customer ✑ The customer is responsible for their information and data, their secure transmission, integrity, and encryption ✑ Also, the customer is responsible for managing, support, patching and control of the guest operating system and AWS services provided like EC2 ✑ AWS customers retain control and ownership of their data ✑ The AWS network provides significant protection against traditional network security issues and the customer can implement further protection Reference: https://www.whizlabs.com/blog/aws-security-shared-responsibility/","discussions": "44"}, "Question #76 Topic 1":{ "question":"Where should a company go to search software listings from independent software vendors to find, test, buy and deploy software that runs on AWS?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Marketplace", "B. Amazon Lumberyard", "C. AWS Artifact", "D. Amazon CloudSearch"],"explanation": "AWS Marketplace is a digital catalog with thousands of software listings from independent software vendors that make it easy to find, test, buy, and deploy software that runs on AWS. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com","discussions": "2"}, "Question #77 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is a benefit of using the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Permissive security removes the administrative burden.", "CORRECT:B. Ability to focus on revenue-generating activities.", "C. Control over cloud network hardware.", "D. Choice of specific cloud hardware vendors."],"explanation": "Developer and IT staff productivity accounted for nearly 30% of overall financial benefits. The remaining benefits were driven by the flexibility and agility of Amazon cloud infrastructure services, which make it easier to trial new business models, support revenue-generating applications, and provide more reliable services to end users. Reference: https://media.amazonwebservices.com/IDC_Business_Value_of_AWS_Accelerates_Over_time.pdf","discussions": "4"}, "Question #78 Topic 1":{ "question":"When performing a cost analysis that supports physical isolation of a customer workload, which compute hosting model should be accounted for in the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Dedicated Hosts", "B. Reserved Instances", "C. On-Demand Instances", "D. No Upfront Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "Use Dedicated Hosts to launch Amazon EC2 instances on physical servers that are dedicated for your use. Dedicated Hosts give you additional visibility and control over how instances are placed on a physical server, and you can reliably use the same physical server over time. As a result, Dedicated Hosts enable you to use your existing server-bound software licenses like Windows Server and address corporate compliance and regulatory requirements.","discussions": "3"}, "Question #79 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides the ability to manage infrastructure as code?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CodePipeline", "B. AWS CodeDeploy", "C. AWS Direct Connect", "CORRECT:D. AWS CloudFormation"],"explanation": "AWS CloudFormation provides a common language for you to describe and provision all the infrastructure resources in your cloud environment. CloudFormation allows you to use a simple text file to model and provision, in an automated and secure manner, all the resources needed for your applications across all regions and accounts. This file serves as the single source of truth for your cloud environment. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #80 Topic 1":{ "question":"If a customer needs to audit the change management of AWS resources, which of the following AWS services should the customer use?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Config", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. Amazon CloudWatch", "D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "AWS Config is a service that enables you to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources. Config continuously monitors and records your AWS resource configurations and allows you to automate the evaluation of recorded configurations against desired configurations. With Config, you can review changes in configurations and relationships between AWS resources, dive into detailed resource configuration histories, and determine your overall compliance against the configurations specified in your internal guidelines. This enables you to simplify compliance auditing, security analysis, change management, and operational troubleshooting. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/config/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #81 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is Amazon CloudWatch?", "answers":[ "A. A code repository with customizable build and team commit features.", "CORRECT:B. A metrics repository with customizable notification thresholds and channels.", "C. A security configuration repository with threat analytics.", "D. A rule repository of a web application firewall with automated vulnerability prevention features."],"explanation": "Amazon CloudWatch is basically a metrics repository. An AWS service '' such as Amazon EC2 '' puts metrics into the repository, and you retrieve statistics based on those metrics. If you put your own custom metrics into the repository, you can retrieve statistics on these metrics as well. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/cloudwatch_architecture.html","discussions": "5"}, "Question #82 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service allows a company with multiple AWS accounts to combine its usage to obtain volume discounts?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Server Migration Service", "CORRECT:B. AWS Organizations", "C. AWS Budgets", "D. AWS Trusted Advisor"],"explanation": "use the consolidated billing feature in AWS Organizations to consolidate billing and payment for multiple AWS accounts or multiple Amazon Internet Services Pvt. Ltd (AISPL) accounts. Every organization in AWS Organizations has a master account that pays the charges of all the member accounts. Consolidated billing has the following benefits: ✑ One bill '' You get one bill for multiple accounts. ✑ Easy tracking '' You can track the charges across multiple accounts and download the combined cost and usage data. ✑ Combined usage '' You can combine the usage across all accounts in the organization to share the volume pricing discounts and Reserved Instance discounts. This can result in a lower charge for your project, department, or company than with individual standalone accounts. For more information, see Volume Discounts. ✑ No extra fee '' Consolidated billing is offered at no additional cost.","discussions": "2"}, "Question #83 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "CORRECT:B. AWS OpsWorks", "CORRECT:C. AWS CodeDeploy", "D. AWS Batch", "E. AWS X-Ray"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codedeploy/latest/userguide/instances-on-premises.html https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/opsworks-on-prem-and-existing-instances/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #84 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which Amazon EC2 pricing model adjusts based on supply and demand of EC2 instances?", "answers":[ "A. On-Demand Instances", "B. Reserved Instances", "CORRECT:C. Spot Instances", "D. Convertible Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "In the new model, the Spot prices are more predictable, updated less frequently, and are determined by supply and demand for Amazon EC2 spare capacity, not bid prices. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/compute/new-amazon-ec2-spot-pricing/","discussions": "10"}, "Question #85 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Use manual monitoring.", "B. Use fixed servers.", "C. Implement loose coupling.", "CORRECT:D. Rely on individual components.", "CORRECT:E. Design for scalability."],"explanation": "Rearchitecting applications involves sweeping change where an old monolithic application is completely revamped according to modern microservices architecture. Using individual components to re-architect a big application is one part of the process. The most important part is to design the application for scalability because the level of investment for a monolithic application can only be justified when resilience and scalability is needed. Reference: https://www.architech.ca/re-architect-applications/","discussions": "19"}, "Question #86 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that allows for one-hour target response time for support cases?", "answers":[ "A. Enterprise", "CORRECT:B. Business", "C. Developer", "D. Basic"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #87 Topic 1":{ "question":"Where can AWS compliance and certification reports be downloaded?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Artifact", "B. AWS Concierge", "C. AWS Certificate Manager", "D. AWS Trusted Advisor"],"explanation": "WS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS's security and compliance reports and select online agreements. The AWS SOC 2 report is particularly helpful for completing questionnaires because it provides a comprehensive description of the implementation and operating effectiveness of AWS security controls. Another useful document is the Executive Briefing within the AWS FedRAMP Partner Package. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/faq/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #88 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides a customized view of the health of specific AWS services that power a customer's workloads running on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Service Health Dashboard", "B. AWS X-Ray", "CORRECT:C. AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "D. Amazon CloudWatch"],"explanation": "Personal Health Dashboard gives you a personalized view of the status of the AWS services that power your applications, enabling you to quickly see when AWS is experiencing issues that may impact you. For example, in the event of a lost EBS volume associated with one of your EC2 instances, you would gain quick visibility into the status of the specific service you are using, helping save precious time troubleshooting to determine root cause. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/personal-health-dashboard/","discussions": "25"}, "Question #89 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is an advantage of consolidated billing on AWS?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Volume pricing qualification", "B. Shared access permissions", "C. Multiple bills per account", "D. Eliminates the need for tagging"],"explanation": "If you have multiple standalone accounts, your charges might decrease if you add the accounts to an organization. AWS combines usage from all accounts in the organization to qualify you for volume pricing discounts. Reference: https://help.nops.io/consolidated-billing","discussions": "1"}, "Question #90 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following steps should be taken by a customer when conducting penetration testing on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Conduct penetration testing using Amazon Inspector, and then notify AWS support.", "CORRECT:B. Request and wait for approval from the customer's internal security team, and then conduct testing.", "C. Notify AWS support, and then conduct testing immediately.", "D. Request and wait for approval from AWS support, and then conduct testing."],"explanation": "AWS customers are welcome to carry out security assessments or penetration tests against their AWS infrastructure without prior approval for 8 services. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/security/penetration-testing/","discussions": "28"}, "Question #91 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following AWS features enables a user to launch a pre-configured Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Machine Image", "C. Amazon EC2 Systems Manager", "D. Amazon AppStream 2.0"],"explanation": "To use Amazon EC2, you simply: ✑ Select a pre-configured, templated Amazon Machine Image (AMI) to get up and running immediately. Or create an AMI containing your applications, libraries, data, and associated configuration settings. ✑ Configure security and network access on your Amazon EC2 instance. ✑ Choose which instance type(s) you want, then start, terminate, and monitor as many instances of your AMI as needed, using the web service APIs or the variety of management tools provided. ✑ Determine whether you want to run in multiple locations, utilize static IP endpoints, or attach persistent block storage to your instances. ✑ Pay only for the resources that you actually consume, like instance-hours or data transfer. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/features/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #92 Topic 1":{ "question":"How would an AWS customer easily apply common access controls to a large set of users?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Apply an IAM policy to an IAM group.", "B. Apply an IAM policy to an IAM role.", "C. Apply the same IAM policy to all IAM users with access to the same workload.", "D. Apply an IAM policy to an Amazon Cognito user pool."],"explanation": "Instead of defining permissions for individual IAM users, it's usually more convenient to create groups that relate to job functions (administrators, developers, accounting, etc.). Next, define the relevant permissions for each group. Finally, assign IAM users to those groups. All the users in an IAM group inherit the permissions assigned to the group. That way, you can make changes for everyone in a group in just one place. As people move around in your company, you can simply change what IAM group their IAM user belongs to. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","discussions": "5"}, "Question #93 Topic 1":{ "question":"What technology enables compute capacity to adjust as loads change?", "answers":[ "A. Load balancing", "B. Automatic failover", "C. Round robin", "CORRECT:D. Auto Scaling"],"explanation": "AWS Auto Scaling monitors your applications and automatically adjusts capacity to maintain steady, predictable performance at the lowest possible cost. Using AWS Auto Scaling, it's easy to setup application scaling for multiple resources across multiple services in minutes. The service provides a simple, powerful user interface that lets you build scaling plans for resources including Amazon EC2 instances and Spot Fleets, Amazon ECS tasks, Amazon DynamoDB tables and indexes, and Amazon Aurora Replicas. AWS Auto Scaling makes scaling simple with recommendations that allow you to optimize performance, costs, or balance between them. If you're already using Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling to dynamically scale your Amazon EC2 instances, you can now combine it with AWS Auto Scaling to scale additional resources for other AWS services. With AWS Auto Scaling, your applications always have the right resources at the right time. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #94 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Route 53", "B. Amazon EC2", "C. Amazon S3", "CORRECT:D. Amazon CloudFront", "E. Amazon DynamoDB"],"explanation": "Reference: http://jayendrapatil.com/aws-global-vs-regional-vs-az-resources/","discussions": "11"}, "Question #95 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service would you use to obtain compliance reports and certificates?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Artifact", "B. AWS Lambda", "C. Amazon Inspector", "D. AWS Certificate Manager"],"explanation": "AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS' security and compliance reports and select online agreements. Reports available in AWS Artifact include our Service Organization Control (SOC) reports, Payment Card Industry (PCI) reports, and certifications from accreditation bodies across geographies and compliance verticals that validate the implementation and operating effectiveness of AWS security controls. Agreements available in AWS Artifact include the Business Associate Addendum (BAA) and the Nondisclosure Agreement (NDA). Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #96 Topic 1":{ "question":"Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following tasks are the responsibility of the AWS customer? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Ensuring that application data is encrypted at rest", "B. Ensuring that AWS NTP servers are set to the correct time", "CORRECT:C. Ensuring that users have received security training in the use of AWS services", "D. Ensuring that access to data centers is restricted", "E. Ensuring that hardware is disposed of properly"],"explanation": "","discussions": "16"}, "Question #97 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service can be used to manually launch instances based on resource requirements?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon EBS", "B. Amazon S3", "CORRECT:C. Amazon EC2", "D. Amazon ECS"],"explanation": "","discussions": "1"}, "Question #98 Topic 1":{ "question":"A company is migrating an application that is running non-interruptible workloads for a three-year time frame. Which pricing construct would provide the MOST cost-effective solution?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon EC2 Spot Instances", "B. Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances", "C. Amazon EC2 On-Demand Instances", "CORRECT:D. Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "","discussions": "20"}, "Question #99 Topic 1":{ "question":"The financial benefits of using AWS are: (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO).", "B. increased capital expenditure (capex).", "CORRECT:C. reduced operational expenditure (opex).", "D. deferred payment plans for startups.", "E. business credit lines for stratups."],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #100 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS Cost Management tool allows you to view the most granular data about your AWS bill?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Cost Explorer", "B. AWS Budgets", "CORRECT:C. AWS Cost and Usage report", "D. AWS Billing dashboard"],"explanation": "The Cost & Usage Report is your one-stop-shop for accessing the most granular data about your AWS costs and usage. You can also load your cost and usage information into Amazon Athena, Amazon Redshift, AWS QuickSight, or a tool of your choice. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/aws-cost-management/","discussions": "27"}}}